<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC on ASF TAC</title>
    <link>https://tac.apache.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel Assistance Committee - TAC on ASF TAC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tac.apache.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/big_data.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/big_data.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Big Data stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } Big Data stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/build_systems.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/build_systems.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Build System stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } Build System stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/cloud.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/cloud.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Cloud stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } Cloud stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/content.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/content.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Content stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
Content System stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.
 Maxim Solodovnik Piotr Zarzycki Gaurav Saini Sharan Foga Jeff Genender Pedro Giffuni Bhargav Golla   Maxim Solodovnik What&amp;rsquo;s your name?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/http.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/http.html</guid>
      <description>Title: HTTP stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } HTTP stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/andriy_redko.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/andriy_redko.html</guid>
      <description>Andriy Redko What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Andriy Redko
What Apache project are you involved in?
Apache CXF
Where in the world are you from?
Canada
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
For me ApacheCon is all about community. I met so many great people, had a lot of thoughtful conversations, heard about dozens of very interesting projects I had no idea existed. It is a terrific event.
What was the best new project you heard about at ApacheCon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/bhargav_golla.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/bhargav_golla.html</guid>
      <description>Bhargav Golla What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Bhargav Golla
What Apache project are you involved in?
I was involved with Apache PhotArk (Retired project), and Apache Isis, as a Google Summer of Code Developer
Were you a student/academic at the time of ApacheCon?
Yes, I was a student.
Where in the world are you from?
I am a student at Clemson University, Clemson, SC.
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
Being able to meet all the great committers from the community, and listening from each of them first hand about their experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/dammina_sahabandu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/dammina_sahabandu.html</guid>
      <description>Dammina Sahabandu What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Dammina
What Apache project are you involved in?
Apache Bloodhound
Were you a student/academic at the time of ApacheCon?
I was a student at that time
Where in the world are you from?
Matara, Sri Lanka.
What would you say to someone thinking of applying to TAC for the first time?
If you are a first timer you should never hesitate, because you have the highest chance of getting accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/gabriel_brascher.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/gabriel_brascher.html</guid>
      <description>Gabriel Beims Bräscher What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Gabriel Beims Bräscher
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
It was one of the most intense weeks in my life, as I was constantly learning about new cultures, projects, people, places, technologies. To be honest, at first I was afraid (as a young guy, a mere masters student); however, everyone treats you equally, it does not matter who you are and where are you from, because everyone knows that you are part of the ASF community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/gaurav_saini.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/gaurav_saini.html</guid>
      <description>Gaurav Saini What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Gaurav Saini
What Apache project(s)/Open Source Software project(s) are you involved in?
Apache Fineract, Apache OFBiz and Apache Roller
Where in the world are you from?
Punjab, India
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
The best bit about ApacheCon is you get to meet many intelligent minds from around the world. Interesting part going through TAC is you get an opportunity to introduce the speakers and interact in person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/ignasi_barrera.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/ignasi_barrera.html</guid>
      <description>Ignasi Barrera What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Ignasi Barrera
What Apache project are you involved in?
I&amp;rsquo;ve been actively involved in Apache jclouds for about four years, since a little bit before the project joined the ASF. I am the project&amp;rsquo;s current Chair, and about 9 months ago I became a Member of the foundation.
Where in the world are you from?
From sunny Barcelona!
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/jeff_genender.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/jeff_genender.html</guid>
      <description>Jeff Genender What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Jeff Genender
What Apache project are you involved in?
Camel, CXF, ServiceMix, Mina, TomEE, ActiveMQ
Where in the world are you from?
Colorado
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
Great opportunity to meet others on projects from all over the world and put names to faces
Who was the best person you met at ApacheCon, and why?
Everyone… because everyone is cool. ;-)
What unexpected things did you learn at ApacheCon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/keren_ouaknine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/keren_ouaknine.html</guid>
      <description>Keren Ouaknine What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Keren Ouaknine
Which ApacheCon/Apache event did you attend?
ApacheCon in Miami, FL 2017.
What Apache project(s)/Open Source Software project(s) are you involved in?
Apache AsterixDB, Apache Pig
Were you a student/academic at the time of ApacheCon?
Yes, Phd candidate at the Hebrew University.
Where in the world are you from?
Israel
What would you say to someone thinking of applying to TAC for the first time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/maxim_solodovnik.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/maxim_solodovnik.html</guid>
      <description>Maxim Solodovnik What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Maxim Solodovnik
What Apache project are you involved in?
OpenMeetings, Flex, Wicket
Where in the world are you from?
Russia, Siberia
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
I was able to meet new friends, meet lots of people I was emailing with &amp;ldquo;in person&amp;rdquo;, I can now wear an &amp;ldquo;Ask me&amp;rdquo; badge and easily talk to people I never met before :)
Who was the best person you met at ApacheCon, and why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/nitin_kumar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/nitin_kumar.html</guid>
      <description>Nitin Kumar Maharana What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Nitin Kumar Maharana
Which ApacheCon/Apache event did you attend?
ApacheCon and Apache Big Data North America, Miami, Florida, 15th - 19th May 2017.
What Apache project(s)/Open Source Software project(s) are you involved in?
Apache CloudStack.
Where in the world are you from?
India
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
It was an amazing opportunity to meet with techies from all over the world. Listen to their experiences in building large scale open source projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/pedro_giffuni.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/pedro_giffuni.html</guid>
      <description>Pedro Giffuni What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
I am Pedro Giffuni.
What Apache project are you involved in?
I am one of the main developers behind Apache OpenOffice and I am a developer in FreeBSD as well.
Where in the world are you from?
I am from Bogota, Colombia, and I also have Italian heritage.
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
It was no doubt an awesome conference, with a huge variety of projects to choose from and complete tracks to follow many, or perhaps all, of your current interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/piotr_zarzycki.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/piotr_zarzycki.html</guid>
      <description>Piotr Zarzycki What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Piotr Zarzycki
Which ApacheCon/Apache event did you attend?
I attended ApacheCon.
What Apache project(s)/Open Source Software project(s) are you involved in?
I am involved in the Apache Flex project.
Where in the world are you from?
I am from Poland (Cracow).
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
Absolutely one of the best things was meeting people who you know only from mailing lists.
Who was the best person you met at ApacheCon, and why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/rafael_weingartner.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/rafael_weingartner.html</guid>
      <description>Rafael Weingärtner What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
I am Rafael Weingärtner.
What Apache project(s)/Open Source Software project(s) are you involved in?
Apache CloudStack and IOTA
Were you a student/academic at the time of ApacheCon?
Yes, I was a Ph.D. student in Computer Science Where in the world are you from?
Brazil
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
The opportunity to meet great people from all around the world. Not just technical folks, but also people who know how to create and manage huge projects on a daily basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/sharan_foga.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/sharan_foga.html</guid>
      <description>Sharan Foga What&amp;rsquo;s your name (as you like to be called / shown for the interview)?
Sharan Foga
What Apache project are you involved in?
Apache OFBiz
Were you a student/academic at the time of ApacheCon?
No
Where in the world are you from?
I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a global traveller. I&amp;rsquo;m originally from the UK but currently live in the Czech Republic.
What was the most interesting thing you learned at ApacheCon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/yash_sharma.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/interviews/yash_sharma.html</guid>
      <description>Yash Sharma What&amp;rsquo;s your name?
Yash Sharma
What Apache project are you involved in?
I am a contributor to Apache Drill and Apache Calcite, and a committer to Apache Lens.
Where in the world are you from?
India.
What was the best bit about ApacheCon?
The best bit is definitely meeting the best people from around the globe who share the same passion for software and sharing. It&amp;rsquo;s great listening to experienced senior programmers and the interesting use cases they have been solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/iot.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/iot.html</guid>
      <description>Title: IoT (Internet of Things) stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } IoT (Internet of Things) stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/nosql_databases.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/nosql_databases.html</guid>
      <description>Title: NoSQL and Database stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } NoSQL and Datbase stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/students.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/students.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Student and Academic stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } Student and Academic stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/web_framework.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/web_framework.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Web Framework stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } Web Framework stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/women.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/women.html</guid>
      <description>Title: Women&amp;rsquo;s stories from past ApacheCon Travel Assistance Recipients license: https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
strong { color: #303284; font-size: 140%; } Women&amp;rsquo;s stories from past Travel Assistance Recipients This is part of our series of stories from past ApacheCon and Apache Big Data attendees whom the Apache Travel Assistance committee helped be at the event. To learn more about TAC, visit the main TAC page. For more stories, see the TAC stories index page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stories of past Travel Assistance Recipients</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/stories/</guid>
      <description>Stories of past Travel Assistance Recipients  By Project Area By Background   The Travel Assistance Committee helps those who would like to attend ApacheCon events, but are unable to do so for financial reasons.
Over the years, TAC has helped many people, from all backgrounds and from all over the world, attend Apache events. This is a collection of some of their stories.
By Project Area Interested in how people from projects in a certain area found TAC and ApacheCon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/events/</guid>
      <description> Travel Assistance Committee Stories  
Stories from previous successful applicants Stories coming soon!
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/events/current.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/events/current.html</guid>
      <description>Travel Assistance Committee Events currently being supported by TAC  
Currently supported events Berlin Buzzwords 2023
 Applications are now being accepted to attend Berlin Buzzwords taking place between the 18th and 20th June 2023 Event details on their website  The ASF Travel Assistance Committee hopes to offer 5 or 6 Conference Passes along with Hotel and Travel assistance as needed. Assistance is open to anyone involved in Open Source including ASF Committers, non-committer contributors and people from open source projects in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/events/previous.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/events/previous.html</guid>
      <description>Travel Assistance Committee Past events  
Previous events that TAC supported Fosdem 2020, Brussels, Belgium ApacheCon EU 2019, Berlin, Germany ApacheCon NA 2019, Las Vegas, Nevada ApacheCon NA 2018, Montreal, Canada ApacheCon NA 2017, Miami, Florida ApacheCon EU 2016, Seville, Spain ApacheCon NA 2016, Vancouver, Canada ApacheCon EU 2015, Budapest, Hungary ApacheCon NA 2015, Austin, Taxes ApacheCon EU 2014, Budapest, Hungary ApacheCon NA 2014, Denver Colorado ApacheCon NA 2013, Portland Oregon ApacheCon Europe 2012, Sinsheim, Germany ApacheCon NA 2011, Vancouver Apache Retreat Ireland 2011 ApacheCon NA 2010, Atlanta Apache Retreat Hursley 2010 Apache Retreat Ireland 2010 ApacheCon US 2009 Oakland ApacheCon EU 2009 Amsterdam ApacheCon US 2008 New Orleans</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/index_old.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/index_old.html</guid>
      <description>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC  Purpose and intended audience Application criteria  What the assistance covers   Arrangements and planning for successful applicants    How to apply for travel assistance  Events for which support is available  Stories from past TAC recipients  Who are TAC? Past Events   The Travel Assistance Committee helps those who would like to attend ApacheCon events, but are unable to do so for financial reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>