<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on ASF TAC</title>
    <link>https://tac.apache.org/events.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on ASF TAC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tac.apache.org/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/events/</guid>
      <description> Travel Assistance Committee Stories  
Stories from previous successful applicants Stories coming soon!
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/events/current.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/events/current.html</guid>
      <description>Travel Assistance Committee Events currently being supported by TAC  
Currently supported events Berlin Buzzwords 2023
 Applications are now being accepted to attend Berlin Buzzwords taking place between the 18th and 20th June 2023 Event details on their website  The ASF Travel Assistance Committee hopes to offer 5 or 6 Conference Passes along with Hotel and Travel assistance as needed. Assistance is open to anyone involved in Open Source including ASF Committers, non-committer contributors and people from open source projects in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Assistance Committee - TAC</title>
      <link>https://tac.apache.org/events/previous.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tac.apache.org/events/previous.html</guid>
      <description>Travel Assistance Committee Past events  
Previous events that TAC supported Fosdem 2020, Brussels, Belgium ApacheCon EU 2019, Berlin, Germany ApacheCon NA 2019, Las Vegas, Nevada ApacheCon NA 2018, Montreal, Canada ApacheCon NA 2017, Miami, Florida ApacheCon EU 2016, Seville, Spain ApacheCon NA 2016, Vancouver, Canada ApacheCon EU 2015, Budapest, Hungary ApacheCon NA 2015, Austin, Taxes ApacheCon EU 2014, Budapest, Hungary ApacheCon NA 2014, Denver Colorado ApacheCon NA 2013, Portland Oregon ApacheCon Europe 2012, Sinsheim, Germany ApacheCon NA 2011, Vancouver Apache Retreat Ireland 2011 ApacheCon NA 2010, Atlanta Apache Retreat Hursley 2010 Apache Retreat Ireland 2010 ApacheCon US 2009 Oakland ApacheCon EU 2009 Amsterdam ApacheCon US 2008 New Orleans</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>